[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "How are you tonight?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "So the president looks mean there.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "the", "president", "looks", "mean", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ":", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Do you intend to pursue any legislation specifically regarding abortion?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "intend", "to", "pursue", "any", "legislation", "specifically", "regarding", "abortion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I don't -- there's no legislation regarding -- with regards to abortion that I'm familiar with that -- that would become part of my agenda.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "there", "'s", "no", "legislation", "regarding", "--", "with", "regards", "to", "abortion", "that", "I", "'m", "familiar", "with", "that", "--", "that", "would", "become", "part", "of", "my", "agenda", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "So which is it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "which", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "He's referring -- listen.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "referring", "--", "listen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Do you see it as an evolution or do you see it -- see it as a rather cynical exercise?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "it", "as", "an", "evolution", "or", "do", "you", "see", "it", "--", "see", "it", "as", "a", "rather", "cynical", "exercise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "I think -- no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Obama", "Chris Stevens"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Should heads roll?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "heads", "roll", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, first of all, Piers, you know, President Obama knew Ambassador Chris Stevens.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "President", "Obama", "knew", "Ambassador", "Chris", "Stevens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "That it had been planned?", "question_tokens": ["That", "it", "had", "been", "planned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Piers, I -- I can't even believe that you would suggest that Ambassador Rice would make deliberately misleading statements.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "even", "believe", "that", "you", "would", "suggest", "that", "Ambassador", "Rice", "would", "make", "deliberately", "misleading", "statements", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "VBD", "RP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "-- that Ambassador Rice was simply wrong?", "question_tokens": ["--", "that", "Ambassador", "Rice", "was", "simply", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, I think as more information came out, the initial information that would -- that they had was perceived to be that the attack was the result of protests and as the investigation has worn on, which is the responsible way to deal with it, we've come out and the administration has said, well, it's clear that now it was the result of a terrorist attack.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "as", "more", "information", "came", "out", ",", "the", "initial", "information", "that", "would", "--", "that", "they", "had", "was", "perceived", "to", "be", "that", "the", "attack", "was", "the", "result", "of", "protests", "and", "as", "the", "investigation", "has", "worn", "on", ",", "which", "is", "the", "responsible", "way", "to", "deal", "with", "it", ",", "we", "'ve", "come", "out", "and", "the", "administration", "has", "said", ",", "well", ",", "it", "'s", "clear", "that", "now", "it", "was", "the", "result", "of", "a", "terrorist", "attack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "IN", "VB", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "And secondly, what -- why, with the world's intelligence, amass that you have at the White House and the Pentagon and so on, why could you make statements four, five days after (INAUDIBLE) with completely the wrong explanation for what has provoked this attack?", "question_tokens": ["And", "secondly", ",", "what", "--", "why", ",", "with", "the", "world", "'s", "intelligence", ",", "amass", "that", "you", "have", "at", "the", "White", "House", "and", "the", "Pentagon", "and", "so", "on", ",", "why", "could", "you", "make", "statements", "four", ",", "five", "days", "after", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "with", "completely", "the", "wrong", "explanation", "for", "what", "has", "provoked", "this", "attack", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", ":", "WRB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Piers, Piers, because these investigations are complicated and detailed and rather than say absolutely nothing, rather than -- you know, than not give information to the American people, Ambassador Rice went out and talked about what they believed to be happening at the time with the information on -- from the intelligence community that she had.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "these", "investigations", "are", "complicated", "and", "detailed", "and", "rather", "than", "say", "absolutely", "nothing", ",", "rather", "than", "--", "you", "know", ",", "than", "not", "give", "information", "to", "the", "American", "people", ",", "Ambassador", "Rice", "went", "out", "and", "talked", "about", "what", "they", "believed", "to", "be", "happening", "at", "the", "time", "with", "the", "information", "on", "--", "from", "the", "intelligence", "community", "that", "she", "had", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "Pentagon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Pretty un-American to be putting out completely false statements before you know the facts, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "un-American", "to", "be", "putting", "out", "completely", "false", "statements", "before", "you", "know", "the", "facts", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Piers, it is not, it is not OK for you to be saying that the administration was putting out completely false statements.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "it", "is", "not", ",", "it", "is", "not", "OK", "for", "you", "to", "be", "saying", "that", "the", "administration", "was", "putting", "out", "completely", "false", "statements", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "It doesn't mean that it wasn't deliberate.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "mean", "that", "it", "was", "n't", "deliberate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Who could have thought that we'd be in this position?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "could", "have", "thought", "that", "we", "'d", "be", "in", "this", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "No, I --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No, I think both of us secretly thought Barack Obama was cruising to victory.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "both", "of", "us", "secretly", "thought", "Barack", "Obama", "was", "cruising", "to", "victory", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Is that what you thought?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "thought", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "It's funny I was also watching that, I'm thinking, nobody was having more fun during this election than Bill Clinton, you know?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "funny", "I", "was", "also", "watching", "that", ",", "I", "'m", "thinking", ",", "nobody", "was", "having", "more", "fun", "during", "this", "election", "than", "Bill", "Clinton", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Could it in a funny way hurt him?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "it", "in", "a", "funny", "way", "hurt", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "It could hurt him and when I was watching that clip, in fact, I was thinking about animation in Clinton's -- you know, voice and face, and I was thinking about Barack Obama during the last debate where he just look like he didn't want to be there.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "could", "hurt", "him", "and", "when", "I", "was", "watching", "that", "clip", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "I", "was", "thinking", "about", "animation", "in", "Clinton", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "voice", "and", "face", ",", "and", "I", "was", "thinking", "about", "Barack", "Obama", "during", "the", "last", "debate", "where", "he", "just", "look", "like", "he", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "be", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "I mean what is wrong with that position?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "is", "wrong", "with", "that", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "There is nothing wrong with that position.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "nothing", "wrong", "with", "that", "position", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Biden versus Ryan, who's going to win?", "question_tokens": ["Biden", "versus", "Ryan", ",", "who", "'s", "going", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I think because the expectation is heavy that Ryan wins by a lot, I think Biden wins.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "because", "the", "expectation", "is", "heavy", "that", "Ryan", "wins", "by", "a", "lot", ",", "I", "think", "Biden", "wins", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "And Romney-Obama next week?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Romney-Obama", "next", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Again, because of expectations, I think we're going to be talking about how good Obama was because no one -- everyone is going to be comparing it to his last debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "because", "of", "expectations", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "talking", "about", "how", "good", "Obama", "was", "because", "no", "one", "--", "everyone", "is", "going", "to", "be", "comparing", "it", "to", "his", "last", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Governor Romney"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "``", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "''", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "So is this a lie?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "this", "a", "lie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I mean Governor Romney has made very clear that if a bill comes to his desk, that overturns \"Roe versus Wade\" that he will be fully supportive of that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "Governor", "Romney", "has", "made", "very", "clear", "that", "if", "a", "bill", "comes", "to", "his", "desk", ",", "that", "overturns", "``", "Roe", "versus", "Wade", "''", "that", "he", "will", "be", "fully", "supportive", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Which one is he?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "It's not that his position changed, it's that he says that, you know, he -- there is a difference between if a bill came to my desk, I'd sign it and I'm going to go to Congress and fight for a bill.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "that", "his", "position", "changed", ",", "it", "'s", "that", "he", "says", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "--", "there", "is", "a", "difference", "between", "if", "a", "bill", "came", "to", "my", "desk", ",", "I", "'d", "sign", "it", "and", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "to", "Congress", "and", "fight", "for", "a", "bill", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "You don't really care about abortion as an issue?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "really", "care", "about", "abortion", "as", "an", "issue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "No, I think it's an important issue, but I think fixing the economy is the most important thing.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "an", "important", "issue", ",", "but", "I", "think", "fixing", "the", "economy", "is", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What the hell were you doing, Barack?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "hell", "were", "you", "doing", ",", "Barack", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "I'm not going to speculate on what happened in the White House.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "speculate", "on", "what", "happened", "in", "the", "White", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"]}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Or is everyone really waiting for the next one?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "everyone", "really", "waiting", "for", "the", "next", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I don't think Paul Ryan is on the menu.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "Paul", "Ryan", "is", "on", "the", "menu", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What is it about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "It is bipartisan, transatlantic and private.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "bipartisan", ",", "transatlantic", "and", "private", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "How do we get the elevator working again?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "get", "the", "elevator", "working", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Well, we focus on areas where we think the business community can really be involved.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "focus", "on", "areas", "where", "we", "think", "the", "business", "community", "can", "really", "be", "involved", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Should more business leaders be doing this?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "more", "business", "leaders", "be", "doing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Well, I think that, yes, we need to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "need", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Which of the two leaders right now, pound for pound, dollar for dollar, would you say gives the best chance of fulfilling what you would like to see?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "of", "the", "two", "leaders", "right", "now", ",", "pound", "for", "pound", ",", "dollar", "for", "dollar", ",", "would", "you", "say", "gives", "the", "best", "chance", "of", "fulfilling", "what", "you", "would", "like", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I really think we have laid the question down to ourselves of we're asking what the business community needs to do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "think", "we", "have", "laid", "the", "question", "down", "to", "ourselves", "of", "we", "'re", "asking", "what", "the", "business", "community", "needs", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]